shareitforpc.com 2016-07-15

# Privacy Policy - SHAREit For PC

## Privacy Policy – www.shareitforpc.com:-

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 14 March, 2015.  
Yogu operates http://www.shareitforpc.com/ (the “Professional site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving this Site. By using this Site, you agree the collection and use the information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, Get access at http://www.shareitforpc.com/.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: email address. You may however, visit our website anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## Log Data:-

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

## We Use Cookies:-

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Links (From or To) Other Sites:-

Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Privacy Policy Changes:-

We will notify you in an email if any changes occur in our Privacy policy.

## Contact Us:-

shareitforpc@gmail.com.

### Connect With Me In Social’s :-

[Facebook ](https://www.facebook.com/pages/Shareit-for-pc/779486632128843)– [Google+](https://plus.google.com/u/0/b/110973340488815980469/+Shareitforpcdownload) – [Twitter](https://twitter.com/shareitforpc).
